Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Video Recordings, 1993-2005
  - Fales: Through Other Lenses, 2010 Mar 9; cuid1645; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Hartford Institute: voice over recording, 2010 Mar 8; cuid1646; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 2010 Mar 18; cuid1647; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Annual Fales Lecture, 2010 Mar 11; cuid1648; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - GME Program Director' Retreat Resident, 2010 Mar 22; cuid1649; 9 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Nursing Conference: Innovative Applications, 2010 Mar 19; cuid1650; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 88)
  - Fales Food Series: Food Media in New Media, 2010 Mar 25; cuid1651; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - UN: Bill Clinton Speaks about Haiti, 2010 Mar 25; cuid1652; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Social Entrpreneruship in the 21st Century, 2010 Apr 1; cuid1653; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Vitamin A Deficiencies and Global Public Health, 2010 Mar 30; cuid1654; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Stern School of Business, Social Impacting, 2010 Apr 5; cuid1655; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Ashok Sani Lecture: Mark K. Shriver, 2010 Apr 6; cuid1656; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Unigo.com Wall Street Journal Panel, 2010 Apr 6; cuid1657; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - University Professorship Lecture, 2010 Apr 6; cuid1658; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Global Public Health: Mexico, 2010 Apr 9; cuid1659; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Teaching with Technology, 2010 Apr 16; cuid1660; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - New York University's Frederic Ewen, cuid1661; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - SCPS Schack Career Fair, 2010 Apr 20; cuid1662; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Courant Alumni Lecture, 2010 Apr 20; cuid1663; 1 minidvs (Box 89)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Anthony Romero, 2010 Apr 27; cuid1664; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Stern International Studies Program: ISP, 2010 Apr 30; cuid1665; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Africa House: The Rule of Law and Business in Africa, 2010 May 3; cuid1666; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Courant Lecture: Alfio Quarteroni, 2010 Apr 29; cuid1667; 1 minidvs (Box 89)
  - Fales Food Series: Me in a Book, 2010 Apr 29; cuid1668; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - International Public Policy Forum, 2010 Apr 17; cuid1669; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 89)
  - Global Health Capstone Presentations, 2010 May 7; cuid1670; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Courant Institute of Mathmatical Science Lecture, 2010 May 8; cuid1671; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - The Mysteries and Marvels of Memory, 2010 Mar 27; cuid1672; 11 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - SCPS Presentation: Naomi Zigler, 2010 Apr 14; cuid1673; 1 minidvs (Box 89)
  - Fales Food Series: Feed Your Pet Right, 2010 May 27; cuid1674; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - CAS Stuyvesant Intel Presentations, 2010 May 27; cuid1675; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - CAS Stuyvesant Intel Presentations, 2010 May 27; cuid1676; 3 minidvs (Box 85)
  - Secret Gardens: Powerful Plots in Surprising Places, 2010 Jun 17; cuid1677; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - NYU Libraries All Staff Meeting, 2010 Jun 21; cuid1678; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 2010 Jun 25; cuid1679; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 89)
  - BARD High School Early College, 2010 Jun 24; cuid1680; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 89)
  - MetroCenter's 2010 Technical Assistance, 2010 Jul 9; cuid1681; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 89)
  - Presidential Welcome and Reality Show at Radio City, 2010 Aug 3 (Box 89)
  - Institute of Art and Civic Dialogue: Anna Deavere Smith, 2010 Oct 16; cuid1682; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - CAS Parent's Day Video Overflow, 2010 Oct 23; cuid1683; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 90)
  - Fales: Mary Ellen Solt Reading, 2010 Oct 27; cuid1684; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Interactive Arts Performance Series: Ear to the Earth, 2010 Oct 27; cuid1685; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Derek Jeter Podcast, 2010 Oct 28; cuid1686; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy: Amartya Sen, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1687; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Fales Food Series: Back into the Kitchen, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1688; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - George Stoney Tribute, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1689; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Casa Italiano Anniversary, 2010 Nov 4; cuid1690; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Courant Alumni Lecture: Vladimir Vapnik, 2010 Nov 9; cuid1691; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Silver School of Social Work: 50th Anniversary, 2010 Nov 11; cuid1692; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Tamiment Library: Philip Agee, 2010 Nov 9; cuid1693; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Pedagogy and Theatre of the Oppressed, 2010 Nov 12; cuid1694; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Commonweal Magazine Conversations, 2010 Nov 12; cuid1695; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Parents Day Simulcast, 2010 Oct 23; cuid1696; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - DNP Leadership Class Lecture, 2010 Nov 21; cuid1697; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Martin Fischer, 2010 Nov 29; cuid1698; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Jacob J. Javits Visiting Professorship, 2010 Dec 7; cuid1699; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - The Women's Conference, 2010 Oct 26; cuid1700; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 90)
  - A Conversation with Gordon Brown, MP, 2010 Dec 14; cuid1701; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - New Trustee Induction Ceremony, 2010 Dec 13; cuid1702; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - The Future of Nursing with Kristie Gebbie, 2010 Dec 13; cuid1703; 1 minidvs (Box 90)
  - Courant: 75th Anniversary Holiday Lecture, 2010 Dec 16; cuid1704; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - An Evening with Senators Tom Daschle and Trent Lott, 2011 Feb 2; cuid1705; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - America at a Crossroads: The dayton Accords, 2011 Feb 9; cuid1706; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - Sheikh Mohamad bin Zayed Scholars Program, 2011 Feb 5; cuid1707; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - A/P/A: Midnight on the Mavi Marmara, 2011 Feb 16; cuid1708; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - Third Annual Global South Asia Conference, 2011 Feb 16; cuid1709; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - Stern: Social Impacting Corporate Social, 2011 Mar 21; cuid1710; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - SCPS: McGhee Egyptian Panel, 2011 Mar 22; cuid1711; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - Reynold Speaker Series: Food Panel, 2011 Mar 23; cuid1712; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 91)
  - PLACEMARKER BOX 92, cuid1713 (Box 92)
  - Starworks Foundation Showcase with Jonathan Safran Foer and Matthea Harvey, 2011 Apr 8; cuid1714; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Fales: What's the Matter With Mass Produced?, 2011 Apr 14; cuid1715; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Fales: Visual Aids, What Comes Next?, 2011 Apr 20; cuid1716; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - NYU's Inaugural Distinguished Global leader Residence, 2011 Apr 4; cuid1717; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Courant Lecture: The Search for Randomness, 2011 Apr 7; cuid1718; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Presidents Service Awards, 2011 Apr 27; cuid1719; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Wagner: Gordon Brown at Stern, 2011 Apr 8; cuid1720; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Stern: Entrepreneur Competition Awards Final Pitch and Ceremony, 2011 Apr 29; cuid1721; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - UDAR: Alumni Luncehon University Development and Alumni Relations, 2011 Apr 6; cuid1722; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Courant 75th Anniversary Celebration, 2011 May 6; cuid1723; 9 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Business and White Collar Crime, 2011 Apr 25; cuid1724; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Institute of Public Knowledge Conference: Designing Mobility for Democracy: The Role of Cities, 2011 Apr 14; cuid1725; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - NYU Trustee's Pre Commencement Dinner, 2011 May 17; cuid1726; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Courant Summer Conference "Games for Change", 2011 Jun 20; cuid1727; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 2011 Jun 24; cuid1728; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Stern Lunchtime Leadership Speaker Series, 2011 May 26; cuid1729; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Stern ISP: Final Presentation Competition, 2011 May 6; cuid1730; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Speakers on the Square: Mossette Broderick American Guilded Age, 2011 Jun 13; cuid1731; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Metro Centeres Technical Assistance Center of Disproportionality, 2011 Jul 6; cuid1732; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - SCPS Media Talk Magazines:The New Conversations, 2011 Jun 14; cuid1733; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Learning Leaders: Real Superheroes of NYC Public Schools, 2011 May 11; cuid1734; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Trends in Literary Translation, 2011 Apr 16; cuid1735; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Stern Entreprenuer Competition Awards, 2011 Apr 29; cuid1736; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Fales: From Here to Harvesting, 2011 Jun 9; cuid1737; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 93)
  - Welcome Week Class of 2021 Recording, Including Address by Former Dean of Admissions Shawn Abbott, 2017; cuid1738 (Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_RG_38-16-1-1_ER_1)
- Series II: Commencement and Founder's Day, 1995-2009
  - 163rd NYU Commencement, 1995; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 16, Reel Project 74)
    Barcode: 31142042272891
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1995, 33 videocassettes (Box 27, Box 101)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day, 1996; 20 videocassettes (Box 28)
  - Founder's Day, 1997; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272867
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 5, Reel Project 19)
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 5, Reel Project 19)
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 1 videocassettes (Box 5, Reel Project 18)
  - Gallatin Commencement, 1997; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 16, Reel Project 72)
  - 165th NYU Commencement, 1997; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 16, Reel Project 73)
    Access copy
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 12:20
  - Bagpipes for Commencement, 1997; 1 sound cassettes (Box 21, Reel Project 77)
    Barcode: 31142042272941
  - Commencement & Founder's Day, 1997; 14 videocassettes (Box 29)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1997; 9 videocassettes (Box 30)
  - Grad Alley, 1998; 3 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 13, Reel Project 65)
  - 166th NYU Commencement: JumboTron, 1998; 1 videocassettes (Box 13, Reel Project 66)
  - Founder's Day, 1998; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 14, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272875
  - 166th NYU Commencement, 1998; 4 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 16, Reel Project 66)
  - Stern Undergraduate Pre-commencement Footage, 1998; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 21, Reel Project 64)
  - NYU Grad Alley, 1998; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 19, Reel Project 65)
    Barcode: 31142042272925
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 23 videocassettes (Box 31)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 13 videocassettes (Box 32)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 9 videocassettes (Box 33)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1998; 8 videocassettes (Box 34)
  - Founder's Day, 1999; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
  - Founder's Day Master, 1999; 2 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272883
  - 167th NYU Commencement Master, 1999; 1 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 71)
  - 167th NYU Commencement, 1999; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 16, Reel Project 71)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day, 1999; 11 sound discs (minidisc) (Box 35)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1999; 9 videocassettes (Box 36)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1999; 11 videocassettes (Box 37)
  - Stern Undergraduate Precommencement, 2000; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 13, Reel Project 64)
  - 168th NYU Commencement, 2000; 10 videocassettes (Box 13, Reel Project 67)
  - 168th NYU Commencement, 2000; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 14, Reel Project 67)
  - 168th NYU Commencement, 2000; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 14, Reel Project 67)
  - Stern Graduation, 2000; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 14, Reel Project 64)
  - Founders Day, 2000; 2 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - Gallatin Commencement Master, 2000; 2 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 72)
  - School of Continuing & Professional Studies Commencement, 2000; 2 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 75)
  - 169th NYU Commencement, 2001; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 14, Reel Project 70)
  - Founder's Day, 2001; 3 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - 169th Commencement Exercises NYU 2001, 10 May 2001; 2 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - 169th NYU Commencement Master, 2001; 4 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 70)
  - 169th NYU Commencement Master, 2001; 11 videocassettes (Box 17, Reel Project 70)
    Barcode: 31142042272909
  - 169th NYU Commencement, 2001; 10 videocassettes (Box 18, Reel Project 70)
    Barcode: 31142042272917
  - Gallatin Commencement Master, 2001; 2 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 72)
  - "School of Continuing & Professional Studies Class Day Exercises Master, 2001; 1 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 69)
  - Founder's Day, 2002; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
  - 170th NYU Commencement, 2002; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 13, Reel Project 68)
  - Founder's Day, 2002; 4 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 14, Reel Project 63)
  - Founder's Day Master, 2002; 3 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - School of Continuing & Professional Studies Commencement Master, 2002; 4 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 69)
  - 170th NYU Commencement, 2002; 8 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 68)
  - 170th NYU Commencement, 2002; 18 videocassettes (Box 20, Reel Project 68)
    Barcode: 31142042272933
  - 171st NYU Commencement, 2003; 12 videocassettes (Box 21, Reel Project 76)
  - 171st NYU Commencement, 2003; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 71, Reel Project 76)
  - 171st NYU Commencement Master, 2003; 8 videocassettes (Box 22, Reel Project 76)
    Barcode: 31142042272958
  - 172nd NYU Commencement Master, 2004; 7 videocassettes (Box 23, Reel Project 78)
  - Gallatin Graduation 2004, 10 May 2004; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - College of Arts & Sciences (CAS) Commencement Master, May 11, 2004; 3 videocassettes (Box 23, Reel Project 80)
  - 172nd NYU Commencement Master, 2004; 17 videocassettes (Box 24, Reel Project 78)
    Barcode: 31142042272974
  - 173rd NYU Commencement Master, 2005; 16 videocassettes (Box 25, Reel Project 81)
    Barcode: 31142042272982
  - 173rd NYU Commencement Master, 2005; 6 videocassettes (Box 26, Reel Project 81)
    Barcode: 31142042272990
  - NYU College of Arts and Science Bacculaureatre, 5 Dec 2005; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - CAS Baccalaureate Ceremony, 4 Dec 2006; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - 2006 Steinhardt Commencement Master, 22 Jun 2006; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2006, 22 videocassettes (Box 38, Box 103)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 14 videocassettes (Box 39, Box 102)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 10 videocassettes (Box 40)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 11 videocassettes (Box 41)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 8 videocassettes (Box 42)
  - The Churchill School Graduation, 22 Jun 2007; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 12 videocassettes (Box 43)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 17 videocassettes (Box 44)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 15 videocassettes (Box 45)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 0 videocassettes (Box 46)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 12 videocassettes (Box 63)
  - Commencement 2008 (Box 83)
  - CAS Winter Baccalaureate, 8 Dec 2008; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - 2008 Steinhardt Doctoral Commencement, 12 May 2008; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 69)
  - Commencement 2009, 24 videocassettes (Box 82, Box 86)
  - Commencement 2009 (Box 85)
  - Commencement 2009 (Box 84)
  - NYU Logo: Torch 1831, undated; 1 videocassettes (betacamsp) (Box 13, Reel Project 61)
    Barcode:31142042272867
  - NYU Logo: Bobcat, undated; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 13, Reel Project 61)
  - Silver Convocation, undated; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 13, Reel Project 62)
  - School of Continuing & Professional Studies Ceremonies, undated; 3 videocassettes (Box 14, Reel Project 69)
  - NYU Logo: Torch Master, undated; 1 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 61)
  - NYU Logo: Tiffany, undated; 1 videocassettes (Box 21, Reel Project 61)
  - Unlabelled Commencement, undated; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 26, Reel Project 82)
  - CAS Winter Baccalaureate, 2010 Dec 6; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - 1996 Commencement Video Rough Cut (Box 94)
  - NYU Commencement 1996: ISO CAM 3 Tape 2 (Box 94)